[{"answer": "How could she forget I've been ordering lunch every day here for 3 and a half years? Is there something you're not telling me because I'm getting a really weird vibe. Is my friend getting rid of me? It's OK I won't say anything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Ah, you don't know anything. You see,", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I remember he made you wear a jock on your head for a whole class. And the straps were hangin' down by his ,..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I had him for Hygene. Remember his teeth. It was like from an exhumed corpse", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Your underwear was stick'n out of your shorts during gym class", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Boxer shorts, ha? Well what brand", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You got any coffee", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yeah. Coffee", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah. Coffee", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yeah, you don't drink coffee? How about instant coffee", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yeah, you don't drink coffee? How about instant coffee", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You don't have any instant coffee", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Tropic of Cancer", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Tropic of Capricorn", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah. You don't have to be quiet. Listen to the ech", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "HELLO", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "HELLO", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "HELLO", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "HELLO", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "HELLO", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend want's to see me in his office SEE ME! That can't be goo", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Maybe I'm getting' a wedgie", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "So I said,", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "It was", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Your underwear was stick'n out of your shorts during gym class", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Boxer shorts, ha? Well what brand", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Oh? So, I took your suggestion and I gave my boss my friend's poems. The ones that affected my friend so much", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Library.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No, ... he didn't! No, ... he didn't", "qsentId": 28}]